Look around there, look around. I see a lot of new faces.
Shut up!
Which means a lot of you have been breaking the first two rules of Fight Club.
Man, I see in Fight Club the strongest and smartest men who have ever lived.
I see all this potential.
And I see a squander.
God damn it, an entire generation pumping gas, waiting tables, slaves with white
collars.
Advertising, hesitation, cars and clothes. Working jobs we hate so we can buy
shit we don't need.
We're the middle children of history, man. No purpose, no place.
We have no great war, no great depression.
Our great war is a spiritual war. Our great depression is our lives.
We've all been raised on television to believe that one day we'd all be
millionaires and movie gods and rock stars.
But we won't.
We're slowly learning that fact and we're very, very pissed off.